<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	
	<content contentuid="h6289eb57g511fg444bga60dg59205c12baa7" version="1">You were schooled in the transmutational art of Alchemy and became quite recognized for your talent. You have access to the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="ExperimentalAlchemy"&gt;Experimental Alchemy&lt;/LSTag&gt; passive feature.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3c9481f1g4033g4a4cg83d5g2e1b595b611f" version="1">Alchemist</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h44c37d5bgda5fg49eeg9ed1ge76f3f52f81d" version="1">You were very young when you discovered your natural talent for speaking with animals. Because of this, you've come to respect and appreciate all animal life and are one to strike up a conversation with any you see. You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_SpeakWithAnimals_SpiritSeeker"&gt;Speak With Animals&lt;/LSTag&gt; on yourself at will without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd0409078gdd8dg4eb5ga703g3178abc0d58d" version="1">Animal Collective</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h2fbaec76g5391g4792gac11g82d9e0b3153f" version="1">You spent much of your adult life away from your homeland, living among people different from your kin. You came to understand these foreign cultures and the ways of their people, who eventually treated you as one of their own.</content>
	<content contentuid="h456a59aag5ef3g47ffg9f00g0c069cf733f8" version="1">Anthropologist</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h93778fdbg4da7g44c4g8498ge5795b664c01" version="1">You spent much of your young life crawling around in the dust, pilfering relics of questionable value from crypts and ruins. As long as you can remember, you've been obsessed with the secrets of the past.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb2278e4g620fg40a7gb2ebg426786fa0bfb" version="1">Archaeologist</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h3cabc88cgcc45g4811g96b6g6f202d38efa0" version="1">You've spent most of your days in the preferred seclusion of libraries and archives, poring over the tomes within. As a result you may be considered smart by your peers, but they don't invite you to parties.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0745980bgefdfg4465g8fffg80a575ae040a" version="1">Archivist</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h5051e746g9573g43a5gbe19gaebdc2549883" version="1">You are significantly older than you look due to spending much of your life in the Astral Sea without aging. You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_UNI_MistyStep_DrowCommander_Amulet"&gt;Misty Step&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;, but returning to the physical world has left you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Vulnerable"&gt;Vulnerable&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Psychic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd987d82cg943bg40d6gbc2cg5ccff18302c7" version="1">Astral Drifter</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hcb05605fg67c0g418dgaef2g37e1b244d57c" version="1">You've spent your days tracking wanted criminals and debtors in exchange for coin. You status is directly tied to your infamy among criminal circles. You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_MAG_HuntersMark_Grymskull"&gt;Hunter's Mark&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h696ecd83g64a8g4418gaae5g4765e837bd6b" version="1">Bounty Hunter</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h6be30d02g328dg45d3ga627gb81e79c2a402" version="1">You were trained and employed in the art of cartography. With a keen eye and a sense for scale, your reputation is built upon the products of your labour.</content>
	<content contentuid="h843dd630gd578g4d0bga491gbd056065085a" version="1">Cartographer</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hbd4c557cg7124g4999g8247gb4fd6a49177e" version="1">You've served your community and acted as the first line of defense against criminality. You are not a soldier, instead your corrective gaze is directed inward: toward stopping the cruelty your own neighbours inflict upon each other.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3d93b593ge844g4e06gbc74gd8bec1248780" version="1">City Watch</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hab76b7bag71e0g4f1bgb9d3g1ead7e7e283b" version="1">You made your living as a courier for the city postal service. Much of your time and effort was spent traversing long, sometimes dangerous, environments..</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c7dbb44g5a1cg4356g828fgae4b6181329e" version="1">Courier</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h908c0386g4132g4042g8e18g8c9e1f01abe5" version="1">You made your living as a private investigator, taking on missing person cases or recovering lost valuables. For your efforts, you've received recognition as someone quite skilled at reading people.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3192b829gacf1g4416gbb7agf0d43252866b" version="1">Detective</content>
	
	<content contentuid="haea994f6g1a3dg4527g85edgbbc549666b7b" version="1">You made a deal with a fiend from one of the Nine Hells. You've been granted superior ability in all skills, but a piece of your soul has been lost forever.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1227eb4cgab97g404ag98f7g43cf7d88551e" version="1">Devil's Bargain</content>
	
	<content contentuid="he3a75c40g20c1g4d71gb5d9g06704cc7bb76" version="1">Your bread and butter are odds and probabilities. You look to take chances at every opportunity. You have access to the &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="Halfling_Lucky"&gt;Halfling Luck&lt;/LSTag&gt; passive feature regradless of race.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0da64376gebf1g44beg8833gc8b838e77671" version="1">Gambler</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h8c05c256g910fg44cegbda6g962b85dc507e" version="1">You spent a part of your life as a combatant in the Black Pit Arena, where you had to kill to survive. The experience left you with many scars, some of which still linger.</content>
	<content contentuid="h50a06905g8947g4800gafa6g003db0377326" version="1">Gladiator</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hde1df695ga9efg4415gb182g151368b9a7e9" version="1">You had some form of direct interaction with a powerful diety in your past. The experience has gifted your mind with incredible fortitude but enfeebled your physical form, leaving you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Vulnerable"&gt;Vulnerable&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all types of Physical damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h48845f89ge009g46b5g8f2ag3c29b90ad229" version="1">God-Touched</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h0b6e7effga36fg40c4g811ega14b00e36d6c" version="1">You were part of a group of criminal bandits that would rob stagecoaches. Separating many a bauble from young maidens and shedding the lifeblood of soldiers, your reputation is one carved in violence. You gain access to the &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_ViciousMockery"&gt;Vicious Mockery&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Cantrip"&gt;cantrip&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hefe4a182g4a55g4d75g92c6g7e9f916b87c9" version="1">Highwayman</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h2becec1agcd97g4696gad8ag541ac14afbb7" version="1">You were part of a small band of mercenaries, killing in the name of whoever had the most coin. Some may call you unscrupulous but really you're just practical.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4a7cc859gad5dg4101gb554g07148788e3a9" version="1">Mercenary</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hb73504e9g8a9dg473bg972eg768994d4d9f8" version="1">You made your coin by selling goods to the fair folk who frequented your stall. While the experience has awarded with you with a relatively comfortable lifestyle, the content life of a merchant has left you slightly squeamish around violence.</content>
	<content contentuid="h72114976g3e83g4410gb089gada97336cb63" version="1">Merchant</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hc35b9c69g1f44g4e78g9bb7ga968dda3b047" version="1">You were trained by an underground circle of thieves who specialize in the art of distraction. Your status is tied to the infamy of the name the people use to refer to your kind: Ninja. You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_FogCloud_Ninja"&gt;Fog Cloud&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="LongRest"&gt;Long Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h14911392g386bg4c05g8c9agc09c19b1b9e1" version="1">Ninja</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h7cb95702g269ag4a9dgbad1g95aadd030ad0" version="1">You've sailed along the Sword Coast pilfering small villages of their valuables. The reputation of a pirate is one of absolute ruthlessness to both civilian and criminal alike.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc7d29019g818eg4267g915cg485b833641c9" version="1">Pirate</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h13650c7fgc43dg4b87gab09gf57d4d59d726" version="1">You made your living as a professional fighter in legal competitions. While your physical form may be hard to rival, a few too many blows to the head has left your mind a little scrambled.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha5c30c07gfdb3g4382gb12fg826d0ed7d4d9" version="1">Pugilist</content>
	
	<content contentuid="ha9b8f371gb1c2g46eegacc2ge67cd4045852" version="1">You worked on a ranch outside the city hauling cattle and tending to livestock. It may not seem like it to city-folk but, it's a rough-and-tumble lifestyle.</content>
	<content contentuid="h42714a1cg066dg4801ga4e5gee30e0aac40d" version="1">Rancher</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hda824f6ag793ag46a1gac1cg73d7a0032376" version="1">You spent your days at sea working for the captain of a shipping vessel. Sailors can be a rough lot, but the responsibilities of life on a ship make them generally reliable as well.</content>
	<content contentuid="haa613d33gff14g406ega4e3gd57137fb1c15" version="1">Sailor</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h91213d8cgcbf8g4417g867dgaf92448dff01" version="1">You've spent your days shaping the minds of the next generation, earning the respect of the local children. You gain access to the &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Guidance"&gt;Guidance&lt;/LSTag&gt; &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Cantrip"&gt;cantrip&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h31efdbafg28aeg4465ga81dg093573ec80a1" version="1">School Teacher</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h3443555cg4b5fg437bg9625gab188d033d51" version="1">You are of a non-humanoid race who has kept their true identity secret for as long as you can remember. Blending into normal society, you don't know any other life, but you still remain ever vigilant of hiding your true self from the world. You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_DisguiseSelf_MaskOfManyFaces"&gt;Disguise Self&lt;/LSTag&gt; at will without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="haffad818g33c2g4e68g97bfga769d399fbbc" version="1">Secret Identity</content>
	
	<content contentuid="hc1606583g9259g471cg9f56gb69a9af95c49" version="1">You are no ordinary criminal, but rather one specialized in the art of deception. By gaining trust, spies work their way into inner circles to the benefit of someone else.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1108e91g51ccg4adagb818gf91b8609b0af" version="1">Spy</content>
	
	<content contentuid="" version="1"></content>
	<content contentuid="" version="1"></content>
</contentList>